mr. woman think CEO of Prudential
Insurance mr. mayor CEO of credential
BSN the top agent joint chairman of VP
Healthcare Group another rasa use of
chairman of adi health honorable and
distinguished guests ladies and
gentlemen it gives me a great pleasure
and pride to be standing here today to
commemorate this wonderful on the ship
between dr. tu and prudential assurance
and prudential BSN dr. tu was initially
launched in october 2015
as the technology to serve the internal
needs of BP Healthcare Group today we
have over 450,000 users with eight
figures in revenue really we have
emerged and continuously sustained as
the number one medical app on both Apple
iOS and Google Play Store in Malaysia
when we first started out we only had
one call feature and that is the doctor
home visit feature now we have grown and
we have many other services now we have
over seven core services and namely
number one doctor home visit number two
ambulance
number three medication delivery
number four video consultation number
five electronic medical records I'm a
six free live chat a number seven
ecommerce we don't that you our mission
is to build a patient centric model
where we put customer in the sensor and
we come up with many various services
around patient and how do we achieve
that is to leverage some technology to
deliver that as a whole and we integrate
vertically with PT Healthcare Group the
brick-and-mortar sign of the health care
industry and packaged it up without of
the two technology to deliver as a
package to our customer and this has
been a great achievement
be serving be patient all of a Malaysian
we would like to extend this to many
other partners and we are very thankful
to Prudential surance and Prudential PSN
for having faith and giving us this our
journey to revolutionize healthcare
technology has allowed us to scale to
new heights in this respect you know we
are very proud in this recent
achievement that we have partnership
with Prudential Insurance and Prudential
BSN and this partnership will see doctor
to you to provide over three million
customers agents and employees of
Prudential Insurance and Prudential BSN
first our convenient pre policy health
screening services and second our
exclusive discounted rates for dr. phone
visit and I just like to share with you
it's not on my on my script here you
know me as a CEO I really see that the
things that we're doing here doctor to
you is not about you know monetary money
and value but actually empowering
patient a lot of patients that users you
know they have their elderly patients
they are immobile they are disabled and
we bring can conveniently to the
doorstep and we really give the family
of peace of mind and every time I see
customers the users and give us great
feedback it released encourage me and my
team to to work harder and to deliver
better to our customers
and the future is looking extremely
bright for dr. tu and we cannot express
enough how excited we are for 2018 we
will continue to work hard and serve and
please our customers and we would once
again like to thank Prudential Insurance
and Prudential BSN what is wonderful
[Applause]